Oyez Press Records
© 2002 University of Connecticut
- Series V: Printing Blocks, undated
  - Unidentified Blocks (Box 18)
    - not identified (5 pcs.)